olwebdesign.com 2013-05-30

# Privacy Policy

### General information

Privacy Policy of Olwebdesign is used in order to protect its customers privacy and security of information stored and shared with us through www.olwebdesign.com. This policy explains clearly how we collect , use and maintain your personal information. By registering and using our site you give consent automatically to use and disclose information if needed. Unless you agree with any terms below, you should not use products or services offered by Olwebdesign.

### Information collection and use

It is essential to collect your personal information in order to be able to make any purchase at Olwebdesign. It would be impossible to make purchase unless you share personal information with us. It is required to provide us with data in the form of username and password to be able to enter our website. At the moment of registration, you give us consent to send you some informative e-mails. Additionally, your data has to be used while accessing technical support and it is required to make consent to this. Apart from that, in case of issuing invoices or other documents, the buyer is obliged to inform us about his/her detailed personal information; such as name, address.

Except the use of your personal data for administrative and analytical purposes, it is allowed to use it in case of some legal actions. Protection and defense of the rights or property of Olwebdesign are taken into consideration, as well as, merger or other business actions.

### Correcting/Updating Personal Information

You are free to update your information at any time directly through our Site. At your request, Olwebdesign will change your information; we may request evidence of your identity before doing so. Inasmuch as your information will never be used without your explicit consent, we are not able to update the email address to which you subscribe to Olwebdesign communications on your behalf. Should you wish to update the email address in our site. Log in at http://www.olwebdesign.com and click on "Your Details" link.

### Protection of personal data information

Organic Law 15/1999, of December 13th, for the Protection of Personal Data. Royal Decree 1720/2007, of December 21st, approving the implementing Regulation for Organic Law 15/1999, of December 13th, for the protection of personal data.

Information gathered and stored at olwebdesign.com is fully protected. We do our best to secure data collected and do not disclose to any unauthorized person. All data is restricted to Olwebdesign employees and external service providers only and they are entitled to use your personal information, however, it is forbidden to misuse this data. If anyone uses classified data in the wrong way, we will take appropriate disciplinary action. 

However, we do not take responsibility for data used during PayPal payment as your personal information used there is not registered by our system and has to be protected by PayPal security system.

### Consent to disclose data

We need to have consent to disclose your personal information because it is impossible to make any purchase without it. If you do not agree to share this data with us, it will be barely possible to offer you any of our products.

At any time, you may inform us about not willing to share with us your personal information and disclosing it. However, because of that fact our services offered will be restricted. Apart from that, there are some situations where we are forced to use your personal information despite the fact that you withdraw your consent to disclose your information.
